And for the ultimate Browns gear, head
to the Browns Pro Shop. A fanatics
experience right next to Huntington Bank
Field. Jerseys, hats, hoodies,
collectibles, exclusive merch you're not
going to find anywhere else. Shop in
store online at shop.cl browns.com. The
Browns Pro Shop, official merch for true
Browns fans as we get into hour two of
the program. And we kick it off with a
little higher or lower, better or worse
college football edition in honor of
spring football, I do presume, which is
underway around the country, by the way.
Very exciting. Very exciting. Um, isn't
this the also the perfect example of
it's it's kind of a microcosm of one of
the million things college football has
just done weird and wrong forever. You
are aware that they have four weeks of
practice that they are allowed and have
been allowed for the by the NCAA forever
for spring football. They get four
weeks. They all do what Ohio State did,
which is one week of practice,
spring break, and then three weeks of
practice as opposed to just four
straight weeks.
>> Just started after
>> started after.
>> Yeah.
>> Inevitably, they're going to follow an
NFL model and it'll be in May and
they'll get the calendar right. That's
where they're all going. So then it
won't have anything to do with the
portal and all of that. But as it stands
right now, if you are a a college
football program of any regard, you are
getting one week a week off and then
three weeks or two weeks, one week, two
weeks. So
>> it's a good way to test, you know, who's
really dialed in, who's going to spring
break and forgetting everything that you
did. By the way, I must say it's a
little distracting. Your the shirt
brings out the a little bit of green in
your eyes.
>> Yeah, you like
>> they're very blue, but today's is very
Yeah, it's
>> very green today. It's all the green I
had. It's
>> which made all the sense.
>> Made all the sense
>> Tuesday. Uh, a little higher, lower. Hi,
Gibbe.
>> Hi. Good to see everybody.
>> Don't give him that look. You guys,
>> that's the internet with that kind of
blue steel. That was green steel is what
we're calling it.
>> Yeah. I just seeing who's paying
attention.
>> Yeah,
>> you have to. Yeah. Pay be pay very close
attention.
>> Sleepy hollow representing.
>> There you go.
>> I'll probably represent this earlier in
the week, too.
>> You want to wear it twice.
>> That's right.
>> I think you should wear it twice.
>> I'm going
watch me.
uh power rank in college football's top
25 coaches in 2026
>> from our great friend Bruce Feldman at
the Athletic.
>> Okay,
>> by the way, sidebar before we get into
this great spring football story. I was
paid by BG. My buddy was the video
coordinator.
>> Okay.
>> And he goes,
>> "Oh, he didn't go up in one of those
lifts. Get back."
>> And he goes, "You want to do this?" I
was like, "Whatever." He goes, "We're
going to pay you like two grand and
we're going to give you like a grand in
gear." Nice.
>> And I was like,
>> I'll take that.
>> I'll take that. Nike deal.
>> Sounds like three grand.
>> Does. Yeah.
>> In a cherry picker up in the end zone.
>> You were. I told you. Don't do it.
>> Three years later, someone died.
>> Yeah. Brian Kelly.
>> Notre Dame.
>> Notre Dame. Yeah.
>> I was in a cherry picker.
>> The wind right up against 75 and the
stadium on the other side.
>> At one point like he comes over and he's
radioing me. He goes, "Y'all right up
there."
>> I go, "Why?" He goes, "I can't even see
your eyes. Are can you even see?" I go,
"I'm afraid I'm going to die. That this
thing's going to blow over."
>> Yeah.
>> And And it was like an old like lift
truck. Like I had to put the legs down.
I had to operate the whole thing. Fine.
Great. I'm dumb and not knowing any
better.
>> Oh gosh.
>> I'm up there. I filmed practice for two
years. It's a great gig.
>> Oh my gosh. Gibbe.
>> But it was uh it was crazy.
>> Now they do it with It's all drones.
>> Yeah. A lot of times it's drones now.
Yeah, you just fly the drones or a lot
of high school teams have drones now.
>> Did you see the from the players? They
had a guy way up in the sky who was like
catching the ball out of the air and
taking it down the green. It was like an
awesome view.
>> No. Where was the camera?
>> Oh, was it a drone? Was it a drone or
guy was up there?
>> People were making jokes like the lift.
>> Brian Kelly would have loved this
particular
>> Gosh, jeez. It was terrible. Yeah.
>> Are we sure it wasn't the blimp? Because
the dude, there was a guy like
>> with a camera up there and he was like
>> up in the sky like it felt like a
hundred feet in the air
>> like with a in a crane or something on
like a giant scissor lift
>> and then he would get the ball like out
of the air and then they were that's how
they were getting those cool shots where
the ball was like coming down from the
camera to the green.
>> Oh, okay. So, they were getting that.
Yeah, they've come so far in golf
broadcast. It's unbelievable how good it
is. I always
>> I I I mean I have so many great friends
at the memorial and um I I don't want to
ever discourage I you know go enjoy it.
It's a festivity. It's fun.
>> Drink your cocktails. Have a good time.
>> But boy, the at home experience on golf
is so superior.
>> It's elite.
>> Yeah. Like if you go to an event, you
have two choices. You either park at a
you have three really. You park at one
hole. You just So, do you just sit at
the green or do you if you can find a
spot where it's a par4 and you can see
where the first where the drive lands
and also get a view of the green if it's
close enough like number nine I'm
thinking at Mirfield's like that the one
that's downhill if you could be perched
like on the opposite side you could see
it land and then you could see it land
on the green but
>> so when I was at Mirfield I was per I
sat just to the side of 14 green
>> yeah that's elite
>> and so You could see yours. It's not a
super long hole. So you could see the T-
shots, see their approach, which was a
very delicate approach shot to the
green. And then you could also watch
people tee off of 15.
>> Perfect. The part. So you got like
>> a But then, you know, once the last
group comes through there, there goes
nothing.
>> Yeah, that's that's prime. That's my
favorite hole on that whole course is
14. That's I just love how you have to
play it with various different ways. Um
especially for them.
>> The other thing you could do is you
could follow one group. Like I've done
that before and that's kind of cool.
It's hard though to get, at least in my
experience when I've done that before.
It is very cool, but it's
>> there are people that are claiming the
hole, so you're never in the best spot.
>> I said that from the perspective of
forgetting that I always have an inside
the ropes badge.
>> Yeah.
>> So,
>> yes. Then you can It's incredible. Then
it's great.
>> Then it's great.
>> Outside the ropes though, you're like
>> you're stuck. It's a lot of walking too
outside. You don't realize how far you
have to walk around where if when you're
inside the ropes, it's pretty good. Oh,
there she is.
>> There she is. Luminaries. Luminaries
walking around.
>> Little L.
>> Little L. In many ways,
>> many. Um, the third thing would be to go
to a party hole
>> and if you're in like one of the sky
boxes, that's fun, too. You can
>> I will say
so at at Murefield, if I'm not mistaken,
those are like on one
and 18
>> uh party holes.
>> Yeah.
>> No, no, no, no, no, no. Uh, the par 316
14 has
>> 16. Okay. I never made it.
>> The par 316 has is a party hole or is a
skybox hole. Okay.
>> Uh 14 now has sky boxes.
>> I guess I was thinking of I'm thinking
of the
>> You're think you're thinking like the
>> those cottages or whatever.
>> Oh yeah. Yeah. Those are down one
fairway
>> where people have hosted. So I've been
in those places before.
>> Yes. You can't see anything. No, you
can't see anything.
>> Nothing. No. I'm talking about like if
you're in one of the luxury brands or
they have like the suit that they build
where you're up there. Those are pretty
good. Like there we used to do our golf
show on Saturday mornings when I worked
at ESPN Cleveland.
>> Yep.
>> We did our golf show from the memorial.
>> Yeah.
>> And the great Jimmy Hanlin.
>> Sure.
>> Hope you're well. Would set us up at a
buddy's house in one of those backyards
right there.
>> Yeah.
>> We would broadcast and two doors down
was Jack Hannah. And Jack Hannah would
come and hang out with us. That's great.
>> While we did the show, I mean, it's like
7 in the morning. Our show was 7 to 9.
>> Yeah. So, literally I'm driving down at
like 5:00 a.m. Yeah. If I wasn't able to
stay with my buddies in Columbus the
night before.
>> Sure.
>> And I'm like, "What is going on? Jack
Hannah's hanging out at 7:05 in the
kitchen. We're making pancakes and the
show's on the air."
>> Okay. I'm in a random guy's house
cooking breakfast.
>> It's amazing.
>> Yeah.
>> So, it's it's good. But the the
>> the at home is you know your way around
a griddle.
>> I do.
>> Of course he does. Of course he does.
Yeah. There's I I couldn't agree more.
at home is I mean it's probably cool to
go there and you want to get some merch
like that's fun.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> That's when we played the Jags. We
actually stayed at Sawrass.
>> Oh, okay.
>> Yeah. I wonder if we would get to do
that again this year.
>> Last time we played them. That's where
we stay. We stayed at Sawrass. So, I
walked over went to the broch. I got a
nice viori like little TBC at Srass
number.
>> Yeah.
>> The one thing that's interesting to me
is that and I know they try to spruce up
their merch which was a epic fail this
year, but like their logo should be that
the green. They still use the like basic
TPC logo with the TPC and the golfing
guy and then it just says Sawrass under
it. They should have like the par three
like the island green as like a logo
like everything when I was there. This
was two years ago was week two a season
ago. Yeah.
>> Just that TPC guy. This the PGA TPC with
>> Sass and it says Sess. That's it. That's
the logo.
>> Yeah. That ain't it.
>> No. Like
>> that's a huge fail. the the true island
green in Celane like the logo for the
for that course is the island green.
>> Exactly.
>> Yeah,
>> that's right.
>> So that's what they should do. They
should have a silhouette of the island
>> of course
>> of that of that green.
>> What they should do is have a silhouette
of that and then where the pin flag
would be it should be a like a palm tree
coming up out of it.
>> There you go. Now you're talking
sawrass solved. Yeah.
>> Yeah. The last time Yeah. We got there
and like an hour later it was like a
tropical storm and it never let up until
we left on Sunday. talked about the
sport second most cuz you had you were
correct the one I keep calling Mystic
Rock but it's not Shadow Creek in Vegas
is number one Srass number two most
expensive round in the country I
it's wild I'll tell you right now like
it is not it is not any it is less fun
than the one I played in Celane
>> for sure
>> for sure less fun
>> it it's probably in a little better
condition but I mean we played Cordelane
in June, so I don't know what it looked
like.
>> It's not a great I really don't think
it's
>> I just think it's very average. And I
the idea that you would I don't
understand it. Scratching out a cool G
to go
>> Oh, like beat up pebble.
>> No, there's spy glass.
>> No.
>> Oh, no. No, no, no.
>> All right. What movie is this from?
>> They call it Vista View. There's no
vistas and there's certainly no view.
>> I don't know. White Men Can't Jump.
You've se there's a couple that you've
seen a lot. I've seen White Men Can't
Jump obviously several times.
>> Is it Sydney Dean? Is that his name?
Dean. That's where he lives.
>> Billy Hily and Sydney Dean. I would say
it's been 25 years since I've seen Can't
Jump. And I think I've only seen it once
or twice.
>> Like not enough.
>> Did Jeopardy pay some money for the
making of that film, do you think? I
think Jeopardy said we will grant you
the use of Jeopardy
carb blanch and then in return we get
the promotion. That's what I think.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> Why not?
>> Foods that start with the letter Q.
>> She was throwing heat. A lot of heat.
>> Rosie. Rosie had a lot of heat through.
>> That's right.
>> Yeah. On that note, a little higher
lower just right at number one. Can you
guess on the power rankings college
football Nate? Who's the number one head
coach?
>> What am I hard of knowing who the number
one coach is? The guy that just won the
national championship without a single
fivear Kurt Signetti.
>> That's it. He's
>> I mean, how could he not be number one?
>> He's at number one.
>> To be the man, you got to beat the man.
He's currently the man.
>> Not only And it pains me. And he beat
some big teams.
>> He sure did. um two years in a row. It
pains me to admit it, but like number
one almost isn't high enough
>> for what he did
>> for to to go to Indiana in two years.
And I know they had the money, but to be
able to correctly
identify transfer portal kids who would
who under his systems would elevate
themselves is remarkable. Absolutely
remarkable. Yeah. He's the one that's
that's the list.
>> He goes from number 19 to number one.
Yeah,
>> and rightfully so. At number two is
Kirby Smart from Georgia. And it takes
us to number three and the head coach of
the Ohio State Buckeyes, Ryan Day.
Should he be higher, lower, or is he
just right? College football Nate.
I think it's probably it might be just
right, but I think that there's a big
gap between him and anybody else under
him. these three at the top and then
>> and then a and a massive gap.
>> Yeah.
>> You know, Kirby Smart,
>> I don't know. I I think Kirby Smart's
probably appropriately ranked at two two
titles in the last five years.
Buckeyes with one and the Buckeyes you
would say with when you kind of watch
the National Football League and you
watch the way that the NFL drafts unfold
that you'd say that yeah winning one is
and by the way only because of a change
in the rule that season like Ryan Day
had that rule not changed Ryan Day is
not on this list.
>> You mean the 12 team playoff? Yes. Yeah,
you're right. They're not No,
>> he's not on the list.
>> He's not He's on the list. It's one
through 20, but he's not third. I don't
know that he's at Ohio State. So where
is He's somewhere else.
>> Oh, I see. It would that would have been
>> if they lose to Michigan and that ended
their season, I think he's out.
>> That would have been a very interesting
>> I mean, you know better than I do. It
would have been very expensive.
>> Best not talked about publicly, but that
would have been a very interesting time.
>> Yeah. So, he's in some ways very
fortunate to be on this list. now he won
it but I would say
unfortunately
they have in some ways done you've won
one national time so it's not the least
but you have done less than your talent
would indicate at least at the next
level and with what you've seen George's
right there with talent as well but
they've won too
>> yes I think um I think based on what
actually happened the last couple of
years Ryan should be two and Kirby
should be three because I think what has
happened with free transfer and NIL is
Georgia is a little slow to adapt to it.
They're still great. I mean, they're
great, but they're not on the talent
monopolization that they were in the
late teens and early 20s. They don't
have that anymore. And he's missed on
some quarterback stuff.
>> Yeah.
>> Like some of the guys that he let walk.
I mean, his starting quarterback for two
years was a starting quarterback in the
national championship game for Miami.
and they were pleased to get him out the
door in Carson Beck. So, I I think
Kirby's program is a little I think it's
trending down. I think Ryan's You're
right. Like, if there isn't a 12 team
playoff, who knows? There is, though,
and they did win it. And I think their
program is in better shape than
Georgia's right now going forward. So
that's an this brings up an interesting
question that college football Nate
would ponder, which is that
>> if you dropped Kirby Smart onto the Ohio
State
operation, like literally you just
swapped the humans.
>> Yep.
>> Are they the same, better, or worse
>> in your opinion?
>> I mean, stylistically, they'd be totally
different. Um, I don't I don't know if I
don't know that there's a big difference
between the two of them in the coaching
aspect of it. This is this is my case
for Kirby's dominance at Georgia. He if
you go this is a misnomer that people at
Ohio State don't understand. It Ohio
State did not recruit at as great as
they are. They did not recruit at the
level that Alabama and Georgia recruited
at at the end of SA and the beginning of
of Kirby.
>> Kirby Smart routinely signed either the
number one or number two recruiting
class in the country. his first four or
five years at Georgia, they had such a
talent stockpile that they had such an
incredible talent advantage and the
Buckeyes do too. But even Ohio State did
not recruit in the trenches defensively
at corner some of the running back
groups that he's had come through there.
There were some of the re I mean it's
just nuts the corners, the safeties. So
I think that that Kirby and Ryan are
pretty similar in terms of
accomplishments. you know, Ryan's has
one less national title, but from a um
from the way that the sport is now, I'd
rather have Ryan Day than Kirby Smart.
And so, I think if we're ranking them
right now, I I would have day ahead of
him.
>> So, I think that under Ohio State has
done a much better job of utilizing the
portal
>> strategically.
>> Strategically to to
>> and they don't have the losses yet. Now,
this year they did. They lost a bunch of
kids this year, but like in the first
two years of the portal, they did not
lose kids the way Georgia lost kids.
Yeah,
>> Georgia lost a lot of kids.
Yeah. I just think the one thing for me
when you look at um I thought it was a
computer the whole time. That was my
phone which I didn't even know that.
>> Where do you Where did you get that ring
on your phone? Notifications.
>> Well, I had turned I had turned the
ringer on in case Gibbe needed to
>> get me quickly.
>> Yeah.
>> So, I forget turn Yeah, that sounded
like a Windows. I thought Windows like
what the heck is that? Um
>> they've done a better job of that
certainly. I do think when you said
Kirby it would be a different offense, a
little more open, right? a little more
fun, I would say, at times for Kirby.
>> No, he's pretty pessimistic offensively.
>> So, do you think he would have handled
>> he he just wants to play defense?
>> Would he have handled Michigan
similarly? Cuz I think there are a
couple of those losses that were
definitely on.
>> So, Kirby has the same stuff. He can't
beat Alabama.
>> Yeah. So then, no,
>> I mean, he has the same situation. Like,
I think he beats everybody but Bama.
>> I think right now we have
>> But I think it's those three.
>> I think Signetti is in his own tier then
>> for what he did. It's unbelievable what
he did. It's just
>> less.
>> Yeah. I don't It's just going to be
fascinating to see like if he can.
>> I don't know that he can,
>> but right now he's the king. It's crazy.
>> I know a lot of people who went to
Indiana and it's unfathomable to them
that this is their
>> reality. Dude, I covered the Big 10 for
almost 20 years now. It's impossible.
>> Impossible. That was the word. They like
this is like it's like a fever dream.
>> Yeah. I mean, I don't even have an a
comparison. Like there's not a
comparison in professional sports for
like for what they've done in two years,
>> right?
>> Up next, guys, at number four is Kalin
Dbor, the Alabama head coach. Higher,
lower, just right.
>> Way lower.
>> Yeah.
>> Alabama's not even relevant. Who's
Alabama?
>> Lanning is six.
>> Uh,
>> would you put him ahead of Marcus
Freeman at seven with Notre Dame?
>> All right. So now you got a group of
guys here in Freeman,
Lanning. I think Freeman and Lanning
are slightly ahead of Crystal Ball. I
know he played for the national title,
>> but I think uh Lanning and Freeman are
slight Lanning for sure is I put Lanning
four.
>> Same.
>> And he's not he's not that dissimilar to
the other to the first the last two we
talked about.
>> Yep.
And then Crystal Ball
Freeman.
I think what Freeman's done at Notre
Dame in two years is crazy. Three years,
whatever it is, is nuts.
>> Landing needs an att
That group of guys we're talking about
here. They're all I think Dbor's I I
talk to Fine Bomb every week and Dbor is
on the seat's hot.
>> Really?
>> It should be red hot.
>> Yeah.
>> The way that the way that semiinal went
>> and they're delusional, too. like they
think it's just going to continue, but
that they don't have NIL. They're not
organized.
>> No.
>> So, them having the most talent like
they had with Sabin all those years is
over.
>> Yeah.
>> It's done.
>> Um, so for this next question, I'm going
to ask
>> more overrated right now. Dabo at number
eight. Yeah. Or James Franklin at number
14.
>> I think Davo at eight is too high. His
program is the cliff. He's It's gone.
He's wy coyote. He fell off the cliff.
>> Yeah. If this was if this was the last
11 years,
>> Yeah.
>> Davos's there because he was two
national titles and four uh top four six
straight seasons from 2015 2020. But if
you take it from after that point, no,
he's Yeah, Dabo would be down on the
list. I think Franklin's fine at 14. I
think there's two guys in the teens that
are too low, one in particular. Um, and
he's not.
>> Who do you got?
>> Kein.
>> Yeah, I want Lane.
>> Well, that's where I was going to go
next.
>> Yeah, he's top 10. Yeah, he's top 10.
>> That's ridiculous. Like, you might not
like him, and I get it. Like, I
completely get it. But you take Old Miss
to the playoff
>> and they win a game.
>> Yeah. Now, I know he didn't coach it,
but like to get Miss like number four in
the country, to have Miss consistently a
top 10 team.
>> Yeah.
>> He deserves way more. Sarkc is probably
too high because he's really done
nothing at Texas.
>> They they got to a national semi-final
two years ago
>> and he's had a ton of talent. They have
all the resources you'd ever want. Um I
think Mike Elco's too low at Texas A&M.
He's a damn good coach.
>> I think Kirk Fence is too low.
>> Kirk Ference is too low, too.
>> Kirk Ference like is doing it with
that's he doesn't have the backing
>> cobling it together, right?
>> I feel like Kyle Whittingham might be
too high.
>> I tell you what, a fast riser on this is
my guy Rhett Lashley at SMU. Beloved
Ponies.
>> The Beloved Ponies.
>> The Beloved Ponies. That That's too low
for him. He should be higher in Willie
Fritz at Houston. Um Lincoln Riley's too
low, too, at 19.
>> What's going on at USC?
>> They're not real organized.
How could they not be?
>> Here's what happened. I mean, this is
really what happened. Like for the blue
blue bloodoods,
>> and this is how Indiana happened, how
Miami happened. They were too slow and
too enamored with high school recruits
for too long.
>> Yeah.
>> And it really took until this year for
Ohio State. Ohio State will pivot next
year. But even the last couple years,
they're they are paying way too much
money for 18 year olds who they don't
know if they can play.
>> Yep.
>> So USC did that, Georgia did it, Ohio
State did it, Texas did it because
forever the big jump, big boost you got
was recruiting titles. What? Where do we
rank in the national recruiting
rankings? Well, it turns out it doesn't
matter anymore. You need four or five
impact guys in a recruiting class. 10 to
12 program. I'll be around. I got your
back. I love playing for the Scarlet
Grey guys. And then you need a portal
class of 15 guys that are dudes. That's
how you do it.
>> Yeah. So, I think Lincoln chased
recruits. They gave money to a bunch of
kids who ended up transferring out. Ohio
State got bit by this. Milin Graham, the
other Quincy Porter, who just went to
Notre Dame last year. They gave him a
lot of money. They're at Notre Dame now.
So, what good did it do you to develop
them?
>> Yeah.
>> So,
>> yeah, you just developed them for
someone else.
>> That's exactly it. So,
>> that's today's edition just so
>> of higher or lower. Little fun one
there.
>> Yeah, it was fun. That was fun. Um, all
right. Your moment of the week coming up
next. You're listen to Cleveland Browns
Daily. We're presented by Valley Bet,
official sports betting partner,
Cleveland Browns. Please bet
responsibly.
And welcome back into Cleveland Browns
Daily. We're presented by Valley Bet,
official sports betting partner of your
Cleveland Browns. Please bet
responsibly. Now, here is Z in your
moment of the week one-on-one with new
Browns guard Zion Johnson.
>> Here with one of the newest members of
the Cleveland Browns free agent signing
guard Zion Johnson. Zion, welcome to
Cleveland. What's this been like for you
so far?
>> I mean, it's been awesome. Uh, very
excited to, you know, tour the facility,
meet all the coaches, uh, you know, I
stayed downtown, so got to see downtown
Cleveland, you know, which was awesome.
And I'm just excited to be here and to
get to work.
>> Yeah. Well, we're certainly excited to
have you, former first round pick.
You've been really kind of an iron man
in your career, played over a thousand
snaps every single season. What's kind
of been the secret to that? And, you
know, we come from, and we look over
there, we see Joe Thomas, guy who played
over 10,000 consecutive snaps, 10,363.
Joel Baton. be like that here in
Cleveland. How have you been able to
accomplish that early in your career?
>> I think at the end of the day, it comes
down to your routine. You know, you have
to have a routine that puts you in the
best possible spot
>> to endure the long season. You know,
whether that's mobility, lifting, uh
your conditioning. Um but I think
there's another aspect to that too,
just, you know, wanting to help the
team, having that grit to fight through,
you know, little ailments, whatever you
may be dealing with to, you know, and
better your organization. Is that
something you take a lot of pride in or
something that kind of your mentality
all along was like, I'm going to be out
there for my guys.
>> Absolutely. Because you want to be out
there for your teammates. You don't want
to let your teammates down and, you
know, that's, you know, something that I
think, you know, players think about all
the time, the team.
>> So, former first round pick, first
opportunity at free agency. What was
that process like for you and and what
about it led you to be sitting here
right now with the Cleveland Browns?
>> Yeah, so, you know, at first it was a
little nerve-wracking. You know, a lot
of, you know, uncertainty, a lot of uh,
you know, options. uh that sort of
thing.
>> Uh but I think what led me here was, you
know, I see a team on the rise. I see a
lot of, you know, pieces, a lot of guys
um with a lot of talent on this team.
Like I recall during the season watching
a game in crossover of the Browns and I
think uh we were running a counter to
the left and uh there was like a holding
call on somebody but uh you know Judkins
like split it for like 60 yards and I
was like man
>> that was in London against the Minnesota
Vikings. I remember that play very well.
Yes. And I was like, "Wow, this this is
a incredible running back." When you see
guys that can like make something out of
nothing. Yeah. And then seeing the
defense, seeing a lot of the pieces on
offense, you know, it just really drew
me
>> and I felt like, you know, as a young
offensive lineman, this is a place I can
come really help this team. Um, and you
know, with Elton and Titus and some of
the other guys that signed really like
establish a culture on the on the
offensive line. So,
>> yeah. Is that exciting for you? Because
obviously, you know, you've had some
familiar faces around you your whole
career. been with the Chargers for the
first four years of your career and now
you're having, you know, Elton was in
Green Bay, you got Titus there in
Houston. All three of you guys, by the
way, playing on playoff teams and good
football teams in your career which
hopefully can bring that, you know, here
and bring some of that winning. But are
you excited to kind of play with some
guys who have been around the league a
little bit and have have had success?
>> Absolutely. I mean, both guys who I've
watched before, seen in crossover, who
have been very successful and played at
the highest level. Um, you know, I think
we all bring, you know, a lot of unique
gifts that we have as players. And I
think these are things we can, you know,
bring together and really, you know,
establish and set a bar for our
offensive line that's at a very high
level.
>> Yeah. And for the last 15 years, this
has been a place that's been about the
offensive line. I think about Joe
Thomas, Joel Batonio, Wyatt Teller,
we've had a lot of guys, Jack Conklin,
you know, Mitchell Schwarz, we've had a
lot of guys, John Greco, Alex Mack, a
lot of offensive line players here.
>> Yeah. to come in and be a part of that
kind of that next generation and kind of
as it you know everything in the league
transitions and this is a new transition
a succession you know to be a part of
that is that something that's exciting
to you and know that you know there's a
there is a a standard here that's been
on the offensive line
>> yeah it's very exciting you know I' I've
watched a lot of Antonio's take
>> very you know very very high level
player
>> so to have the opportunity to you know
come in and you know play a position
that he did and hold the bar hold the
standard um it's something that's you
know very exciting but It's also, you
know, a great challenge that's going to,
you know, push me forward. So,
>> George Warhop is now going to be your
offensive line coach. Been an offensive
line coach for a long time in this
league. Very well respected. And one of
the things he likes to do is work with
what he considers to be very young, very
talented offensive lineman, which you
certainly fit that bill. How excited are
you about that to kind of have that new
perspective and you've seen kind of guys
who have been under him and and where
their careers have gone?
>> Yeah, I'm really excited. Uh, he's one
of those offensive line coaches that,
you know, elite offensive line coach. So
to have the opportunity to play with a
coach of his level, I'm I'm just very
excited to see, you know, what I can
learn from him and, you know, what we
can bounce off of each other and, you
know, how we can, you know, make this
room as good as possible.
>> When you come to a team that's got a
great defense like the Browns do,
>> that probably means practice is going to
be good. And certainly in the training
camp, the iron sharpening iron along
that defensive line, is that one of the
things that you really get fired up for?
It's like, oh man, they're going to kick
Miles Garrett inside on this play. Like,
let's go.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I mean, I think that's
something that, you know, was a huge
draw for me. You know, when I was in LA,
I had the opportunity to practice
against some really good players like
when Bosa was there, when Khalil was
there. Uh, so getting to practice
against, you know, extremely high level
players, you know, like Malik Collins,
like Miles Garrett. Um, and you know,
iron sharpens iron as you said. I I
think that's something that was a draw.
>> What do you want Browns fans to know
about you as a football player? What
kind of guard or what kind of an
offensive lineman? What kind of
mentality do you bring to the field?
Yeah, I think I think my mindset is
relentless. You know, at the end of the
day, you know, a lot of people don't see
the hours, the time spent on the field
working through sets.
>> Um, you know, working through run fits,
trying to, you know, get your technique
to the point where it is on game day.
So, I think, uh, you know, my mindset is
I've already done everything, you know,
required up to game day. I've set a
million, like a thousand times, whatever
it may be. So, now it's time to just let
it loose and, you know, spare no one.
>> Exactly. So, that's kind of the football
you. What's something personal about
Zion Johnson that you want Browns fans
to know? Because this is a football
crazy town. They are going to be
obsessed with you and everybody on this
football team. What's something you want
them to know about you as a person, just
as a guy?
>> Yeah. I mean, I'm a really big family
person. You know, me and my mom are
very, very close. She comes to every
game. That's awesome. My uncle and aunt
come out and, you know, my my girlfriend
of, you know, four years, she goes to
every game. So, I'm a really big family
person. And uh you know that's how I
spend my time when I'm not in football.
Yeah.
>> Are you happy that you're not going to
be in perfect conditions for these
defenders anymore? That now there's
going to be some cold, some elements and
some grass to to muck it up, maybe slow
them down a little bit.
>> I actually missed it cuz uh you know, I
played at Boston College. Uh played in
some cold and some grayer weather and
you know, it feels just like home. Just
like you know, back in Maryland like in
Boston. So
>> yeah. Well, welcome home as it says on
the sign when you're walking around
here. Welcome home, Zion Johnson. and
we're happy to have you on the Cleveland
Browns and uh excited to see what you
can do on the field and get this get
this thing turned around, get this team
winning.
>> Absolutely. I'm happy to be here.
>> Thank you.
>> Awesome, dude.
>> Yeah.
>> And so much more to come. You're
listening to Cleveland Browns Daily.
We're presented by Valley Bet, official
sports betting partner, your Cleveland
Browns. Please bet responsibly.
All right, welcome back in this special
edition of Cleveland Browns Daily. We're
presented by Ballet Bet, official sports
binning partner of your Cleveland
Browns. Please bet responsibly. We've
never done this before. We've never done
this before and I love it. I love the
idea of this.
>> Didn't we open a pack like weren't we at
a card show a couple years ago?
>> Yeah, we have cards of ours.
>> Yeah, they did have cards of ours,
>> but we only had like one pack each.
>> Yeah. Yeah. And you know, I think it was
like old packs. So, we what we have
we're gonna we're gonna open a box. Uh
the kids my kids watch this stuff. Um
all right. So, this is a
>> bonus. Open the box first and foremost.
That's important.
>> Yep.
>> What?
>> The money was Agura breaking the box
open and ripping it open much like he
opens his mail.
>> And it just leaves shards everywhere.
>> Why am I catching right now? Strays and
>> No. No. Am I wrong? G.
Oh, see
>> this is also
>> Hold on. What do you know about the way
I open?
>> This is pretty. By the way, this is
pretty This is also very much a an a
2026. Nice big box, right?
>> Yeah.
>> I'm going to defend them and say that
they think that that then you can like
maybe put your card somewhere or
something. Maybe it becomes a card
holder.
>> I don't know. I don't know about that. I
think what it probably has to do with is
we're going to charge a lot for fewer
>> and so uh I'll let you pick the three
you want.
>> Yeah, we'll just go. So these are NFL
five mega box find five meab box
exclusive pink prisms.
>> So this is 2025. So who would be who
would be who we're looking for?
>> Get on over here. You're the card.
>> Gman. Who who are we looking for? Who
would be like
>> what breaks the bank for us?
>> What's what would be the big winners? I
know the kids love like the downtowns,
but I don't know if those are these.
>> So I've got I've got a couple experts.
I've got the Gman and our IT guru Cory
Blessing who is also infatuated with
cards.
>> Okay. Blessing in the house.
>> Both of these guys are ready to go.
>> What would be So we know what we're
looking for. So we're not bozos. What
What are we looking for? What would be
considered? Oh, baby.
>> What's the rail?
>> Yeah. What are we looking for?
>> What is the case hit in prison? Cy, do
you know
>> what did he the
>> Is it colorast?
>> Color blast is Phoenix.
>> I don't know.
>> I can hear you chewing your gum. What am
I looking for?
>> Let's just open it on something.
>> So, but 2025 would have been.
>> So, is that Travis Hunter and those
guys? That's what it is. Okay. All
right.
>> All right. So, you want to go first?
I'll get I'll give the first let it
breathe. Your first back. Dr. Z opening
it up.
>> All right. We've got
>> Does it have a good hand feel to it?
>> Good hand.
>> Color blast. Color blast and manga are
your prism case hits.
>> All right. We've got a standard. It
looks like a Janu Smith.
>> Okay.
>> We've got a standard rookie Will
Campbell.
>> Okay.
>> Rookie card. Says RC in the corner.
>> People get really jacked up for tackles
in the rookie card business is my in my
history with it. They really get
excited.
>> I don't know about ones with short arms
who gave up 85 pressures in the Super
Bowl, but maybe we'll see.
>> We got a Deontay Thornton Jr. rookie
card
>> of the Raiders. We've got a Honeybadger.
>> Okay.
>> A Dallas Goddard.
>> We've got the newest Raven, Trey
Hendrickson. Just a regular, it appears.
>> Yeah.
>> And a Chase Brown. Just regular.
>> He's just regular this year.
>> Will Campbell. Will Campbell feels like
the best one from that pack.
>> So, not a great pack.
>> That does not appear to be
>> not a good pack.
>> Not a good pack.
>> Will Campbell. You guys
>> YOU'LL GET A YOU'LL GET a couple packs
with just base in them. You guys should
you should grade
A to F the the quality of each pack.
Yeah.
>> What was that pack?
>> That was probably a D.
>> Was a D pack. D.
>> Gross.
>> All right. Uh I start off with a James
Cook base.
>> Mhm.
>> Oh, this one will have a little Oh, I
see pink.
>> Oh,
>> let's go.
>> Oh, baby. Let's go.
>> Um, this one is not pink, but it is a
rookie card. One with local interest,
one Mason Graham. There you go.
>> Oh, baby. There you go.
>> We uh Oh, oopsy daisy. We got an
emergent
rookie card. Travis Hunter.
>> There you go.
>> A Travis Hunter rookie card. Uh number
There it is. Number 12. Number 12. There
you go.
>> Emergent.
>> I don't know what that means. There you
go.
>> Okay. So, uh oh, two pinks.
>> Oh, here we go. Back to back to back.
The first.
Oh, baby.
The old ball coach
>> Steve Spurer.
>> We got to give that to Rudy.
>> This one might have some juice to it.
This is another pink one. This is a
Trayvon Henderson pink rookie card.
>> Good card.
>> We got a good
>> That's a good P.
>> That feels like a massive
>> What are we talking about there? We
talking Is that Is that $500?
>> No. I No. 100 bucks. 40 bucks. 30? I
don't know.
>> 10 bucks. Oh. All right. Theo and then a
Theo Johnson and then a TJ Hawinson.
>> So, what's like the most if we pull
>> I feel like I got four really good cards
there.
>> Yeah, I have zero so far.
>> So far.
>> What's
>> We got to make our money back so I can
expense these.
>> What's the number one?
>> What's the number one card? Like what is
there a card that we could get that does
crazy things for all of us?
>> I mean, you're probably looking for a
color blast or a manga of somebody. So
th those are the inserts that they put
in the like
>> So not that pink. That pink's not a
>> No, that that's a Mega Box exclusive,
though.
>> All right. I have something in here this
time. I see a little color. I see a like
a teal color.
>> Oh, no. I'm showing 99 bucks. No, I'm
not. I'm showing I'm showing 10 bucks
for Trey.
>> Ungraded $2.70.
>> Here we go. Here we go. We've got a
standard Devont Smith.
>> Okay. We've got What was Mike pack? What
was that first pack for me? What' we
grade?
>> Zaguras was a D. Probably a B.
>> Probably B.
>> B.
>> I get nothing fun. I got absolutely
nothing. All right.
>> You got nothing fun again.
>> I got Tyler Warren rookie card.
>> Oh, that's worth thousands.
>> Keemay DK rookie card.
>> Oh,
>> I got a Daniel Carlson regular card.
>> Oh, there we go. Kickers.
>> I got some insert that says I could win.
>> Oh, kid reporter.
>> The kid reporter.
>> Why is that so funny?
This sucks.
It's the greatest ide
>> AJ. Now, this is a weird one. It doesn't
look like it's anything other than
standard,
>> but it's a Ricky Williams Ravens card.
>> Yeah, there's some there's some legends,
some throwback players.
>> To me, the they should make the legends
worth more.
So, so far I've got nothing. You got
like special zero F pack.
>> Oh my god. A D and an F. Good. I picked
well for you at least. the the opposite
of what we did in academia.
>> I think you do you have colors again?
Any colors exciting?
>> All right, here we go. Back at it. Pack
number two.
>> Not even any browns. We got a kicker and
a kid reporter.
>> There you go. Uh maybe we get Mason. Oh,
there's Oh, baby.
>> Lot of color in here. Lot of color.
>> Oh, lots of color for the kids.
>> The girl picked his pack.
>> He did.
>> I did.
>> All right, we're going to
>> But I'm a giver.
>> We're going to kick things off.
>> I wanted to give Bo Bishop the great
packs.
>> A little Travis Kelson.
>> Oh, very nice.
>> Very nice. Cleveland Heights, Ohio.
>> Yep. Uh Jaden Reed.
>> Mhm.
>> Yep.
>> Fine player.
>> You get a Bashard Smith rookie card.
>> Cool.
>> Okay. So, I I don't know if these are
This is the same one I got with Travis.
It's a This is a prismatic.
>> Okay.
>> Omarian Hampton rooker rookie card.
>> So, those are just inserts.
>> Just inserts. Okay.
>> What does that mean? Just an insert.
>> No idea.
>> Just a different take on a base card.
Really?
>> You want to be a There you go,
>> kid reporter.
>> Uh also got a Dave Craig. Nice. There
you go.
>> Little Dave Craig base.
>> He'd fumble a lot.
>> A little He would small hands. Ron
Jorski
>> Jaws
>> and Michael Wilson. That That one was
nothing. That was nothing. Nothing. At
least you have You have gotten I don't
have a single card that wasn't a base
yet.
>> That was C. So, one of these two packs
should be an A.
>> Yeah. One of these
>> one of these two should have a D should
have.
>> One of these should have a memorabilia.
>> I think it's going to be you. I'm
excited for you.
>> No. I feel like I think this is it's
going to go down down and then a at the
end. I can see already. You got a good
one.
>> I got the color. Where's the swearing?
>> I I think you're going to have a jersey
card.
>> Where's Swearen? I got the color.
>> The color.
>> God.
>> T. Higgins regular.
>> Sometimes that was bad news when you got
the color when you saw the color in
Deadwood. Swearen got to you.
>> A Jaydon Blue rookie card.
>> Yeah.
>> A Josh Connorly Jr. rookie card.
>> Tackles, baby. Tackles.
>> Come on. Come on. Give it to
>> this isn't going to be fun for the forar
according to our audience. They're not
going to like this. But this is a pink
>> Odell Beckham Jr.
>> Oh, there you go.
>> There you go.
>> Is it Giants OBJ?
>> Yeah,
>> Giants OBJ.
>> Giants OBJ. Fun card.
>> That's a fun card. What do we got a
value on that?
>> Two bucks.
>> Two buck, Chuck.
>> Yep.
>> Okay, here we go.
>> This is the big one. This is This is the
big one of the
>> This is thick.
>> Yeah, that's a jersey.
>> Come on. Be good.
>> This is a CJ Straoud pink prism jersey
card.
>> Ooh. Oo,
>> yeah. Jersey card. Jersey card.
>> We've got a a standard Wayne Crebette.
>> What a random.
>> I know. And a Jeremy Shaki. I love the
shock man. That That's the best That's
the best card in the box.
>> Hopefully not. Hopefully not.
>> $7 on that Straoud.
>> No. So, Trayvon's better. What about
this Odell? What about this Odell pink
prism?
Seven bucks.
>> This is wonderful.
>> What about Odell?
>> You got to get him graded for the
>> CJ Strad's got to play better in the
playoffs.
>> That'd be one to hold on to.
>> Stock he plays well. And now we're
talking.
>> That's what we call
>> last pack. That's the best one. That's
the best. No, we're not going to get a
card better than that one.
>> Uh we have a Greg Russo
>> standard issue.
>> Can I say something that I don't like?
These these packs are right out of a
box. Never touched. Yeah,
>> there's an a little bit of an arc in
these cards.
>> There is an arc in these cards. Yeah,
>> that you get that with the Prism ones.
Just the way that the paper that they're
printed on. They always come out that
way.
>> Couple of pink ones coming.
>> Okay.
>> Uh not too exciting. A little Graham
Mertz rookie card.
>> I love it. Mertz,
>> a Jade Baron rookie card.
>> Okay. Okay.
>> Gino Stone pink prism. Oh, now we got a
good one. Travis Hunter pink prism
rookie card.
Nice.
>> And then
>> by the way, Dr. Jay looks incredible
right now. He's got like a furlined coat
on.
>> I noticed that when
>> Put him in the mirror. Let me see. Dr.
J,
>> get on the single camera. Get on my
single.
>> Get on my single.
>> Can we get on my single camera?
>> Oh my gosh. Oh my gosh. He looks
spectacular and amazingly slightly
different than what he was wearing in
the previous segment.
>> Yes.
>> Don't know how that
>> similar to them all. Here he comes. Now
come on in. Oh, baby. Look at him.
>> Yes.
>> And then I got Tyreek Hill and I'm Ron
St. Brown.
>> I'm on Ross Brown. I'm
>> on I think but the best this is this is
the I I think this would the best the
two Travis rookie cards. One pink one
whatever and then the Traayvon pink
>> 20 bucks on the Travis Hunter pink one.
>> There you go.
>> Ungraded. These are all ungraded by the
way.
>> That's right. What about And this was
seven. What about the Odell?
$39.
>> $349.
>> So, you had the best you had the best
packs.
>> Act like a motorcycle.
>> Yeah.
>> All right. And what was what was just
for the people out there? Ballpark.
Ballpark. Don't have to be specific.
What was the uh what what's a pack run
you a box run you?
>> $64.99. God.
>> Hey Ricky, I'm filling that expense
report.
>> $64.99. We've got a 20, a 10.
>> These are 10 together. That's 40.
>> Yeah, we didn't make our money. We
might. I don't know. There's the
>> What about the old ball coach?
>> You got an old ball coach, pink prism.
You got a Yeah, there's nothing on the
go.
>> What about a a Will Campbell rookie or a
Taylor war?
>> I think we'd be lucky to be back to even
Stephen, honestly. Very, very lucky.
>> That's the business.
>> Yeah, it is. It's a It's not a great
business. We We did I just did this with
NBC a couple weeks ago, and um it was
two boxes. It was two boxes of tops. You
were you were hunting the Cooper flags
and he's got a ton of the Cooper flag
rookies, but there's some that are worth
like multiple thousands and we were
chasing those and it was like $200 for
like four box like two boxes like that.
>> 200 a box.
>> $100 a box.
>> Jeez Louise.
>> Yeah. And you got like six packs in each
box.
>> So I we have you got one, two, three,
four.
>> I would say those would be the ones.
>> Five. But you and Spurer, you got six at
least like different kind of cards
because you have this Gino Stone too. I
got
>> Yeah. And then I got the Mason rookie. I
only got two.
>> We can get the Mason graded and
autographed.
>> There you go.
>> I say we do that. Then we're on to
things.
>> I'm get Will Campbell autograph. I'll
hold it here.
>> Get close. If you can reach and get it
to get it to
get it to
>> see if he can reach it. All right. Good
job. That was fun.
>> I really enjoyed it.
>> That was a lot of fun. That's a That's a
good time. Uh is it so much more to come
or am I saying we'll see you on down the
road? We'll see you on down the road
then. All right. Thanks for listening
everybody. Okay, that was Cleveland
Browns Daily. We're presented by Valley
Bet, official sports bing partner of
your Cleveland Browns. Please bet
responsibly.
ESPN